[{"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/青椒.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/苹果_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/草莓_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/青苹果.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/指天椒_1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/洋葱.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/南瓜_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/黄苹果.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/包菜_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/苹果_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/黄瓜_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/青苹果.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/花菜_2.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/青椒.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/红椒_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/丝瓜.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/苹果_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/黄苹果.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/黄椒_1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/苹果_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/花菜_2.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/南瓜_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/指天椒_1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/小白萝卜.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/玉米_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/西兰花_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/苹果_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/青苹果.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/丝瓜.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/红椒_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/洋葱.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/黄苹果.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/草莓_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/黄椒_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/洋葱.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/花菜_2.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/小白萝卜.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/洋葱.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/花菜_2.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/梨.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/黄苹果.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/包菜_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/黄椒_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/青椒.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/黄苹果.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/小白萝卜.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/洋葱.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/南瓜_1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/草莓_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/包菜_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/指天椒_1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/黄苹果.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/黄椒_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/花菜_2.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/玉米_1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/蘑菇_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/红椒_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/西兰花_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/梨.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/苹果_1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/西兰花_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/花菜_2.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/黄苹果.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/苹果_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/红椒_1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/土豆.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/小萝卜_2.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/蘑菇_1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/丝瓜.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/草莓_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/南瓜_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/洋葱.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/西兰花_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/青苹果.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/南瓜_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/青椒.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/苹果_1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/蘑菇_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/小萝卜_2.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/草莓_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/土豆.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/苹果_1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/青苹果.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/茄子1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/花菜_2.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/丝瓜.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类填空", "stem": "在蔬菜下面输入“0”，在水果下面输入“1”", "titleInfo": [{"type": "vegetable", "num": 0}, {"type": "fruits", "num": 1}], "content": [{"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/南瓜_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/黄苹果.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/丝瓜.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "fruit", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg", "val": ""}, {"type": "vegetable", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/蘑菇_1.svg", "val": ""}], "type": "au-classify-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-04"}]